Adejare Taiwo

Lagos, Nigeria .adejareemma@gmail.com. +2348079190630

Profile: linkedin.com/in/adejare-taiwo-360956197

Website: https://www.jboy.dev

Summary

Adejare Taiwo is a passionate Software Developer (Backend and Mobile) with proficient knowledge and experience from my previous challenges and hands-on experience using Mobile technologies(Flutter[IOS and Andriod]) Backend language(Nodejs[Express and NestJs], PHP(Laravel) to create and implement software applications. My dream is to be part of the team to learn and build the next big software that will help the tech world at large.

Experience

🔔 Software Developer

Paymyrent.ng

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year +)

- Redesigned and Managed Mobile Application using Flutter(Dart)
- Added More Features to the application:
- * Automated Wallet System
- Managed Deployment on Both Andriod and IOS
- Worked closely with the Team Lead in building other Softwares

Mobile Developer

A1Tutor Ltd

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021 (4 months)

- Worked with the team as Mobile Developer using Flutter(Dart)
- Managed Publishing Applications to Both Apple Store and Playstore
- Worked closely with the Backend Developer to integrate API into the Application

Back End Developer

ProDevs

Jan 2021 - Aug 2021 (8 months)

- Worked closely with the CEO in building several Component on the AVA platform using Nodejs
- Development an automation system for fast payment and processes
- Developed an office management system
- Technologies used: PHP, Nodejs, Mysql, MongoDb etc

Back End Developer

Zedvest TechnologiesAug 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Software Developer Intern

Paymyrent.ng

Jan 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 8 months)

Back End Developer

Flux Technology Africa

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 (5 months)

Back End Developer

HNG Internship May 2020 - Aug 2020 (4 months)

Student and Junior web developer

Self Employed Feb 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

Backend Web developer Instructor

Swap Space Systems Ltd Oct 2019 - Jan 2020 (4 months)

Education

Christ the Redeemer Secondary School

High School Diploma, Science 2014 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

Web Development - Swap Space Systems Ltd

🌎 Php Programming Language - Sololearn

#1059-14583241

Introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS - Udemy

UC-8YVLLSBG

Introduction to Programming Using HTML - Sololearn #1014-14583241

Web development - Udemy

Deno Programming with Typescript - Udemy

Skills

PHP • Node.js • MySQL • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Flutter • HTML • JavaScript • Linux • Vagrant (Software) • Laravel

Honors & Awards

HNG Internship Finalist - Hotels.ng

Sep 2022

Best Student in Mathematics - Christ the Redeemer Secondary School

2014 - 2017

Referees

Abdulateef Gafar - gafar001@mail.ubc.ca

Phone number: 2363308908

Position: Graduate teaching assistant

Ogunyemi Tosin: cutosin@yahoo.com

Phone number: +2348038435443 Position: CEO Paymyrent.ng